Would you or Tony Robbins buy this ladder?
I sell interior design and wellness advisory services
to ultra high net worth families and family offices.
It's currently at 1.6.
And I'm looking to be at 10 million by end of next year
and then scale this to 250 million in the next 10 years.
I have three tiers, $80 a square foot
for renovating or building a new home.
And that includes all of the construction selections,
the drawings, the furniture layout and selection.
Tier two is a seven to 10 year commitment
across their whole real estate portfolio.
And it's $100 a square foot
because we do everything that's included in the first tier.
And then the final tier, tier three,
is the other two tiers.
So we advise on their yacht, their plane, their offices.
I'm not actually sure if a ladder is the approach
I would use with the business you have.
So for fractal pricing to really work,
it needs to be like five times the price.
So like going up by like 20%, it's too undifferentiated.
Your annual retainer should be de minimis.
It should be like a rounding error in this project.
And it should be positioned as insurance.
What it does is it gives you an excuse
to always meet with them every year.
Sell whatever you can get away with.
A lot of people, like if you're a soul at the table,
as long as you give them exactly what they want,
they'll love you, add in the continuity
so that you can keep getting business from them
and it'll stack year over year.
I'll just go $100 a square foot and the continuity
and figure out some features for that.
100's a nice simple number, right?
Very easy to do the math.